<?xml version="1.0"?>
<machines>
	<accelerator>
		<desc>
			As you have already learned, light blue energy is associated most with time and its manipulation. By concentrating this energy and binding it in a crystal structure - a vast improvement over the previous design you scribbled out after slipping and knocking yourself unconscious on a cauldron - you might be able to set up a localized field in which time progresses at a greatly increased rate.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Comes in various tiers, each tier being twice as powerful as the last
			Localized effects may be ineffective over things whose essence is less concentrated
		</note>
	</accelerator>
	<guardian>
		<desc>
			Too often you come home to find your constructions damaged or half of your valuables missing because someone snooping around your property helped themselves to your supplies. Sometimes you are fortunate and have those in power apply magical protection spells over your territory, but they are often of fairly limited range, and the less scrupulous will demand a steep payment from you to do so. Finally, however, you can protect yourself by applying a version of that yourself; each stone emits an aura that prevents those you do not trust from helping themselves to your resources or your structures.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Protects against block placement and breaking, and the opening of GUIs within a %d block range

			Owners and admins always have permissions
			The owner can also use /guardstone add/remove &#60;player&#62; to allow/deny others access <!-- The &# tags are for angle brackets. Do not touch those. -->
		</note>
	</guardian>
	<stand>
		<desc>
			为了那些更宏伟的铸件组合，你需要在3x3的合成网格基础上向外拓展，这就意味着你需要特制容器了。这些环绕在铸件台周围的架子正是你需要的东西，它的存在使得你的网格达到了5x5的大小。外面一圈架子需要抬高一格，这样这些架子和铸件桌之间就没有阻挡了。
		</desc>
		<note>
			
		</note>
	</stand>
	<telepump>
		<desc>
			You already have all sorts of automated pumps and devices to drain large pools of liquid. However, some liquids, irritatingly, occur not in large lakes or wells but in scattered ponds all over the place and thus force you to either bucket it manually or spend more time moving the pump and pipes than actually pumping. The teleportation pump, by using movement energy, solves this problem by draining a large area of disconnected lakes at once, greatly expediting fluid acquisition.
		</desc>
		<note>
			放置后需要对当前区域进行扫描
			每方块基础消耗：
			%s
		</note>
	</telepump>
	<miner>
		<desc>
			Most of your time mining is wasted digging out mountains of rock to find scattered blocks of ore or other valuables, making the whole process a tedious chore that is done more out of necessity than any sort of enjoyment. Even most automated methods of acquiring resources have this problem, wasting a large amount of time and energy, leaving you with nothing to show for it except 50 chests of cobblestone. The mineral extractor, however, is able to sense the presence of value in the world, allowing it to pinpoint the locations of ores and other valuables.
		</desc>
		<note>
			放置后需要对当前区域进行扫描，可用源晶魔杖控制开关。
			每方块基础消耗：
			%s
		</note>
	</miner>
	<reprogrammer>
		<desc>
			有些疯子将暗黑金属打造的笼子散布在了世界的各个角落里，从地下的圆石密室，到古老的矿井，再到下界里红色砖块建成的桥上。从笼子出现的那一刻开始，它们就在生成无尽的怪物，这一点令它们危险，但却给量产怪物掉落物提供了方便。不幸的是，所有那些试图复制笼子结构的人，要么失败了，要么只是得到了一个脆弱的仿制品，能改变笼子中怪物种类的设计更是少之又少。毕竟，你手头能用的，只有堆积如山的腐肉和蜘蛛眼。但是，这台设备的出现，将会改变一切。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</reprogrammer>
	<repeater>
		<desc>
			你在传输流明能量这个问题上迈出的第一步却是个灾难。你做的木质的中继器也只是勉强胜任，而且很容易损坏。说穿了，你从一开始就不应该用木头作为原材料。很明显你大量使用的水晶才是更好的选择。加上一个彩色符文可以帮助它汇聚能量，但这样会让它只能传输一种颜色的能量。也许...你以后会找到第二个问题的解决方法的。
		</desc>
		<note>
			范围：%d方块，含发送和接收
		</note>
	</repeater>
	<weakrepeater>
		<desc>
			The transmission range of a Crystal Pylon is limited to %d blocks, and its beams are blocked by just about anything aside from air and glass; this means that unless you built your base next to one of every pylon - a dangerous endeavour - you need some way to relay the signal. This is exactly the function of a repeater, which can repeat a signal and do so around obstacles. However, repeaters do incur a small signal attenuation, so optimizing the path is a good idea. This is only a first attempt at such repeaters, and as a result its quality is...questionable. Surely you will need to improve your designs with experience.
		</desc>
		<note>
			范围：%d方块，含发送和接收
		</note>
	</weakrepeater>
	<rift>
		<desc>
			Transporting things long-distance or between dimensions is one of the most annoying tasks you have to face; whether you built a structure in another world because of fear of a destructive failure or you are trying to transport a fluid from a source thousands of blocks away to your base, you often find yourself stymied by an inability to bridge the gap. Now, however, you can tie two disparate locations in the world together - no matter the distance or differences in dimension - and transport items, fluids, redstone, power of all kinds, and more through a link to the void.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Always placed in pairs

			What goes in one side of one rift comes out the opposite side of the other

			Item transport is directional, and a side must be chosen with the manipulator
		</note>
	</rift>
	<tank>
		<desc>
			物品很容易就能堆在一块存储－尤其是在你找到了将物品按照一定方式存储进奇异的紫色水晶中后－但是呢，你到现在都还在苦苦寻找存储你收集或者生产出的成吨液体的方式。当然现在你已经有了各种尺寸的储罐，但即便是最大号的那一个，搭建它用到的神奇金属盒子似乎只有在几个预订的尺寸下才能保证整体结构稳定，然后也只能存储数万桶液体。在成功将通向虚空的洞困在玻璃框架中，并注入大量象征流体的魔法能量后，你建成了一座可以快速提升容量的多方块储罐。
		</desc>
		<note>
			容量约为%d*n^2桶，此处n为整个储罐结构中的方块数量

			没有尺寸和形状限制，极限容量可达%d桶
		</note>
	</tank>
	<compound>
		<desc>
			中继器的确是好东西，但它本身也有两个严重问题。其一，若是你有若干水晶塔同时坐落在一条路上，那么你的中继器网络就会变得一团糟。其二，如果你的基地不方便进入的话，你就只能选择打洞以供各个颜色的流明进入。复合灵气中继器成功解决了这两个问题；尽管它体积硕大，并且造价不菲，但它可以同时传输十六种颜色的彩能。同时它们的损耗也有所提高，所以你需要尽量少用这种中继器。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</compound>
	<charger>
		<desc>
			You have already figured out how to make a crystal that can selectively take in and release crystal energy, but you are in need of a way to funnel that energy - which unfiltered would probably violently overload the crystal - safely and efficiently. Recalling something about sharp corners concentrating stress in materials - the details escape you due to the lack of attention you paid at the time (a decision you now regret) - you try to do the same for the crystal, building a frame to shield the edges and focus the energy into the center. As to why it spins...what you don't know can't hurt you, right?
		</desc>
		<note>
			Stores up to %d lumens of each color
		</note>
	</charger>
	<heatlily>
		<desc>
			You, in your (less than) infinite wisdom, decided to make a sugarcane farm in a snow biome. It worked perfectly...until the water froze and your sugarcane rotted on the ground. You need some way to heat the water and stave off the cold in a small area around the farm. Maybe if you used some essence of those mechanical-sounding fire creatures from the Nether bridges, you could make a plant that not only served that purpose, but was aesthetically pleasing as well. This should also help prevent your high-drop landing pools from freezing over. (Ow.)
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</heatlily>
	<ticker>
		<desc>
			你为了一套完美的工具费了不少心思；其中，有些工具是用各种不同材料打造的，这其中包括一些奇异的合金(尤其是那个紫色的坚硬金属，它似乎十分有用)。幸运的是，你可以给这些工具糊上一些青苔，这样做可以似乎可以让它们自行恢复它们的耐久。但问题在于，这青苔似乎是用你的体温驱动的，所以就这样直接把它们丢进箱子里基本没有好处。若是你可以浓缩些生命能量，并再多花点时间的话，你就能造出一个能让它们不在你的背包也能回复耐久的东西，甚至还能回复的更快。
		</desc>
		<note>
			需要：
			%s
		</note>
	</ticker>
	<fence>
		<desc>
			You need some way of protecting your base from the hordes of mobs outside, and fences are rather boring. You already tried using moats (how does a spider the size of a cow swim!?) to no effect, and you tried using unshielding wires as an impromptu electric fence, an experiment that ended after you had the misfortune of touching it yourself. However, with (a large amount of) energy associated with protection and shielding, you can make a barrier that will stop creatures of all types while letting you pass unharmed, and can be built into any shape between connected nodes.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires a perimeter with vertices marked by either fence emitters or relays. Right click with manipulator to calculate perimeter, shift-right-click to set output side
			
			Each emitter in the perimeter adds to the damage dealt to intruding entities
		</note>
	</fence>
	<furnace>
		<desc>
			烧炼。这是世界上最无聊，最普通，但又不得不去做的苦力活之一。的确，现在有很多提高效率的方法－虽然这样做有可能会把一切烧成水－但你也许能借助一种可以同时驾驭火焰和魔法的新熔炉来提高产量。
		</desc>
		<note>
			除锭的粉末外，所有物品均有%d倍产量提升。
		</note>
	</furnace>
	<laser>
		<desc>
			Standard light can be focused into a beam, so it stands to reason that you can do the same with lumen energy with the appropriate lens. That is exactly the function of this device. With it, you can focus energy of any color in a thin beam along a line of blocks - up to %d blocks away - thus applying the effects of that color. Now if only you had any idea what each color did...
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</laser>
	<itemrift>
		<desc>
			有个经典的运输问题，就是两口相隔仅数个方块，且相互之间视线没有阻挡的箱子。你曾经看到过一个设备，贴在带物品栏的方块上后可以快速将其中物品运出，但那个设备的工作范围只有一格；而这一个，正是你曾看到的那个设备的长距离加强版。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</itemrift>
	<crystal>
		<desc>
			Once you started to do a lot of pylon-driven crafting, or started to charge yourself with large quantities of crystal energy, you made a crucial observation: Pylons are not infinite, but lose their color as they are drained. Granted, they do recharge, but slowly - though planting similarly colored trees around them helps a bit. However, you have found that these crystals, being raw elemental energy cast into crystal form, can dramatically increase the charging speed of a pylon, with a full, balanced ring of eight speeding it up enormously.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</crystal>
	<infuser>
		<desc>
			把天然碎片丢入彩能液体中是一回事，而对于净化过的水晶碎片来说就是另一回事了：它对于这样粗暴的对待毫无反应。但你还有更好的策略：使用一种专用的物品容器，将其以彩能液体环绕，然后制造漩涡将彩能液体的能量注入碎片之中。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</infuser>
	<fabricator>
		<desc>
			You have already seen how many items contain trace amounts of various crystal elements, leading you to wonder if the reverse is also true. After much experimentation, you devise an odd contraption that collects crystal energy on large paddles, and funnels it to the center, where it can be formed into an item. You do of course require one item first, as a sort of blueprint, and you note that only some more simplistic items can be fabricated.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires %d*(%.1f*n^%d) lumens per unit naturally present on the item
		</note>
	</fabricator>
	<beacon>
		<desc>
			After an unfortunate encounter with an engine intake, you have been desperately seeking a way to protect yourself from the more hazardous situations you always seem to end up in. Recalling the enormous protective power of %s crystal energy to protect, you try building a beacon that radiates the energy into the air. As long as it stays supplied with energy - not an easy task, given the large energy expenditure - you may well be impossible to kill.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Uses %dn^%d lumens per half-heart of damage
			Max range %d blocks
		</note>
	</beacon>
	<enchanter>
		<desc>
			附魔总是一场令人上火的赌局。你花费了一周时间收集足够多的经验，然后你也许最终得到了节肢杀手I，如果人品好的话你或许能得到时运III和效率V，当然也有可能是略微次一点的附魔组合。但你并没有选择就此放弃－你开始寻找更高效的解决办法，这时你想到了彩能液体，它由经验浓缩而成，也许它能够让你同时达成自动附魔和更精准的附魔控制两个目标。
		</desc>
		<note>
			每级附魔需要%d mB的彩能液体。
		</note>
	</enchanter>
	<chromaflower>
		<desc>
			你或许不是唯一一个造9x9的圆石房子的人，但无论如何，你装修你的家园的能力更多地集中在了使用华丽装饰上，而不是建筑本身上。据此，你将一点水晶能量融入了一朵花中。最终结果很有趣，你得到了一朵绚丽的花，它似乎还有一个特殊功能。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</chromaflower>
	<collector>
		<desc>
			拥有将经验值浓缩并转化为彩能的能力后，你却不是很清楚究竟该怎么做。幸运的是，在你摆弄水晶碎片时，你意外找到了答案；不论是直接让经验球从它上面经过，还是直接从你身上抽取，亦或者直接泵入液体经验，似乎都能催化整个反应过程。
		</desc>
		<note>
			%d XP = 1 mB 彩能液体
		</note>
	</collector>
	<brewer>
		<desc>
			Everyone loves making potions...OK, no. Between collecting a hideous red weed that seems to grow so slowly you could mine a chunk before it grew, to fiddling with arcane procedures that seem designed as a last-resort replacement for something even worse, to burning through valuable ingredients for effects that last mere minutes - and at the expense of a boosted effect too! - nobody sane enjoys this process. At the very least, maybe, you can forgo most of the process by using the energy from the crystal shards instead, making the process actually worth your time.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Standard shards yield Level I 3:00 potions
			Boosted shards yield Level II 8:00 potions
		</note>
	</brewer>
	<ritual>
		<desc>
			You have heard mention of all these special abilities you can gain by imbuing yourself with large quantities of crystal energy, but you need some means to carry out the infusion. After an incident that shall never be mentioned again - and if anyone asks, no, you do not have anything to do with the crater where that village used to be - you recall the shards' infusion process. If it worked for items, maybe it will work for you as well.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</ritual>
	<table>
		<desc>
			木质的工作台，虽然有用，但依旧有它自己的局限性。出于这样的考虑，你找到了一种将水晶粘在工作台上的办法，这样它就可以储存并利用水晶能量了，同时你也得以合成那些需要与魔法能量打交道的物品。你确信这玩意不会要求你用各种头颅环绕其周围，也不会产生各种闪电、爆炸以及剧毒紫色气体，所以你希望这个设计会比你的其他设计更优秀。当然，你一开始并不熟悉这张新的工作台，因此也不能进行一些更高级的合成，但随着你不断地练习与使用，你会乐意去冒险的。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</table>
	<itemcollector>
		<desc>
			Despite your best attempts, you have not been able to totally avert the need for farming, and your mountain of grey seeds and beige goo can attest to that. Unfortunately, farms tend to scatter items far and wide, leading to the need for either powerful item collection systems - which have their own problems - or a problem with so many items on the ground you find it hard to move. The item collector at last is an answer to this problem, being able to collect items anywhere in its range as soon as they are created.
		</desc>
		<note>
			范围：水平方向+/-%d格，垂直方向+/-%d格。
		</note>
	</itemcollector>
	<aishutdown>
		<desc>
			Animal farms are an eternal headache. Between cows' endless noise and chickens' tendency to get out of any enclosure you try to keep them in, you would gleefully exterminate every one of them if not for the fact that you need a supply of leather, feathers, wool, and meat. If there was some way to stun them, to freeze their thought processes, this would probably help a great deal.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</aishutdown>
	<aspect>
		<desc>
			Aside from their use as impromptu musical instruments, those jars of colored liquids you get when melting down random items have an actual use; When you decided to pursue another branch of magic, you found yourself in need of endless numbers of them. The problem is, the process of melting items into raw essentia is slow and hard to automate. With your knowledge of crystal energy, however, you have finally made a device capable of collecting crystal energy and converting it into essentia, though not exactly cheaply.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</aspect>
	<lamp>
		<desc>
			The standard method of keeping unwanted creatures away is to light the area, but that is often difficult or ugly to do, and the best designs can be rendered worthless with one block left a bit too dark. With that in mind, you seek to concentrate crystal energy, being luminous itself, in some sort of lamp to keep the mobs at bay.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Range: %d for each element in the lamp
		</note>
	</lamp>
	<powertree>
		<desc>
			Even with power crystals in place, pylons still remain incapable of handling very heavy load. That, combined with the tedium of venturing to them every time you need to recharge yourself, leads you to dream of a way to store energy in larger quantities, effectively a battery. Obviously a simple box would not be the correct approach, but maybe if you built some sort of structure, it could grow organically. As long as the energy remains pure...
		</desc>
		<note>
			Capacity: %d+%dn^%d, where n is the number of leaf blocks
			Cannot function without a view of the sky
		</note>
	</powertree>
	<lampcontrol>
		<desc>
			You often find yourself in need of controllable lighting, but redstone, even when you figured out how to alloy it into iron and stick it on the ceiling, is clumsy and requires false floors and ceiling in order to hide unslightly wiring. However, the magic aura, which you can control, may allow you to manipulate many separate lamps at a distance, obviating that need.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Max Range: %d
			Max Channel: %d
			Can be controlled manually, with redstone, by the charge state of an RF battery, or with shaft power
		</note>
	</lampcontrol>
	<aspectjar>
		<desc>
			This fabrication process gives you nightmares. Not only is it incredibly unstable - more than once the thing has exploded, sent items flying, or done other nasty things - and to top it off it draws liquid essence out of jars that must be placed around the construct. This would be fine, were it not for the small capacity of these jars, meaning filling them - another tedious process - is a constant necessity. Being able to store more essentia in a jar - perhaps even multiple types! - would be of enormous convenience.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Primal Aspect Capacity: %d
			Other Aspect Capacity: %d
		</note>
	</aspectjar>
	<farmer>
		<desc>
			收割作物可是个不小的麻烦。手动收割不仅速度慢，还效率低下，但那些风扇呢，虽然效率可以，但噪音巨大，并且总是想让物品飞起来。正确地引导那些和自然有关的能量也许可以创造出更好的解。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</farmer>
	<automator>
		<desc>
			Though less of a hassle than some other fabrication systems - that pyramidal altar nearly left you dead on the table - it can still be tedious, particularly with recursive crafting that can take quite a bit of time. This is where an idea hits you - you should be familiar enough with some of these recipes that you might be able to set up some sort of system to automatically perform them, reducing the amount of work by an enormous amount.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</automator>
	<biomepainter>
		<desc>
			你时常发现你需要改变你周围的气候，因为你的工作总需要特定温度和湿度(尤其是那些蜜蜂，你已经证明它们对气候十分挑剔)。你不难想到，用水晶能量就可以达成这个目标，最终你让改变气候就像在帆布上涂画一样简单。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</biomepainter>
	<medistributor>
		<desc>
			That digitial storage system of yours is unmatched in its convenience, except for one thing. Though it has a special device for pumping out items, and another for using internal item buffers to control a redstone signal, doing this with multiple items quickly becomes infeasible. To that end, you have designed an assembly that can function as several of these in parallel, allowing you to always maintain certain item levels in the system.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</medistributor>
	<rfdistributor>
		<desc>
			You thought that it could hardly get any easier with this kind of power; simply hook up the conduits from a generator to a machine and everything worked. However, you were still presented with one final dilemma: When grouping machines together, the cluster of cables is both unsightly and inconvenient to navigate around. Some way to transmit that power wirelessly from above would solve this problem.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</rfdistributor>
	<window>
		<desc>
			有人声称有这样一种窗户，你从中看去，呈现的却是另一端的真实。
		</desc>
		<note>
			需要水晶质石材组成的框架，例如水晶之石、重盾或者黑曜石，同时需要与另一端配对连接。
		</note>
	</window>
	<music>
		<desc>
			How many times have you banged out a tune on the different colors of crystals? With your new device, you should be able to attain even greater musical fidelity, complete with greater range, chord capability, and even - somehow - an oddly familiar melody that came pre-etched into the crystal matrix.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</music>
	<turret>
		<desc>
			若是你每次关门并被苦力怕伏击后都会得到一枚绿宝石，你现在早已能和村民做各种交易了。忍无可忍，无需再忍－你设计了一个迷你设备，可以随时对附近的敌对生物开火，直到目标被消灭。那么现在就只需要高音和斯文了...
		</desc>
		<note>
			需要暴露在天空下，并需要附近有敌对生物作为目标
		</note>
	</turret>
	<pylonturbo>
		<desc>
			You knew you could turbocharge your pylons, but that little display of yours, hopping up and down around the pylon, wildly flailing your manipulator, was neither insightful, productive, nor dignified. Now, however, the pattern is more clear: You need to enhance the structure, building a ring of 8 foci - and one central one below the pylon itself - and trigger the central one with your manipulator. Surely interrupting this process - or breaking the stabilization ring afterwards - is a very bad idea.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Ring: Requires a clear view of the sky and air around it to work; Center: Must be placed 8 blocks below the pylon's orb
		</note>
	</pylonturbo>
	<personal>
		<desc>
			Flying out to each of the sixteen colors of pylon to draw energy from them to power your abilities is a massive headache. Perhaps you could try to imitate them somehow. No doubt you lack the skill - or patience - required to duplicate them exactly, but the end result, if not able to be networked, might still serve as a useful charging point, as well as a nice decoration.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</personal>
	<cloaking>
		<desc>
			Rather inconveniently, you have found yourself largely confined to your base during the night, as it is your only defence against the waves of mobs, which lock onto you the moment you step outside. And this is not counting the time a horde of zombies, detecting the light of your constructions, made a beeline to you and destroyed most of the structure that stood in their way. After much frustration, it hit you: A cloaking device, which makes you undetectable unless at point-blank range. Pleasantly, it even smells of raspberries.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires the tower structure around it to focus its energy and function correctly
		</note>
	</cloaking>
	<lighter>
		<desc>
			Caves are an extremely unpleasant place to be - how many times have you found a large vein of ore, only to be shot into lava, fall down a gravel pit, or be dive-bombed by a creeper? - largely due to their cavernous gloom. Sure, you can cover the entire interior of the cave system with torches, but that quickly gets ridiculous, and after that incident with a gas pocket near the coal vein you wish for an alternative. Knowing that %s energy is that of light, you are sure you can use that to your advantage and make cave-mining actually enjoyable again.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</lighter>
	<reverter>
		<desc>
			你的世界正逐渐崩坏。从降下黑暗诅咒的黑曜石柱，到吞噬一切的紫色野草，你只能眼睁睁地看着曾经美好的一切正缓缓堕落，不再像以前那样友好。甚至那些树造就的魔法森林也会让生物群系一团糟。而你，只是想找到让它们变回原来的样子的办法。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</reverter>
	<cobblegen>
		<desc>
			你从未想到过用光圆石的一天...直到那一天真的来了。的确你现在就可以再挖一些，但你还有别的事情要做。你已经知道将岩浆与水混合即可获得圆石，但它的自动化却是相当麻烦，而且造价不菲。你提出了一种新的解决方案，这是一朵可以自动从附近抽取液体的花，它会把抽到的液体混合起来并将产物直接以物品形式丢在地上。除了圆石，若是配方正确，它还能产生一些别的东西。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</cobblegen>
	<plantaccel>
		<desc>
			Like the proverbial grass and its glacial growth speed, your various flowers and plants to improve the area around them operate at a very slow pace. Perhaps they could be improved upon by being planted on a plant of its own.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</plantaccel>
	<cropspeed>
		<desc>
			Though some crops grow rapidly, the majority - even after careful crossbreeding and hours digging up weeds - very much do not. Already available to you are various means with which to increase that speed, but none of them fit neatly into the farm area itself, instead often requiring being placed nearby. This of course introduces an efficiency penalty, one that would be very desirable to avoid.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</cropspeed>
	<inserter>
		<desc>
			You have repeatedly found yourself manually adding items to constructs that cannot be connected to normal item transport. You long ago tired of dropping stack after stack of sugar into a stone basin, or of berries into a puddle of chroma. You need a way to automate that process before you give up and find something less of a hassle to work with.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</inserter>
	<essentiarelay>
		<desc>
			所以说你现在有了一口装满了水的巫师大锅，你可以往里面倒各种原料，籍此获得你需要的物品。但不论合成成功与否，大量生产总会带来大量有毒气体，于是你又加装了个特殊结构来解决自动化问题，顺带解决毒气问题。但不论如何，你总还是要把源质运输到大锅里的，但你一开始用的管道...和你的想法差太远了。而一套长距离，灵活，稳定耐用的源质运输解决方案－无疑，是极好的。
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</essentiarelay>
	<glowfire>
		<desc>
			Some things you never have enough of, in particular diamonds, shards, and iron (the last of which was not helped by your attempts to build a turbine the size of a small house). Other things you have so much of that your biggest problem is storing it somewhere. What would be most convenient would be to be able to decompose the latter into energy with which you could cast the former. Surely nothing could go wrong with this...
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</glowfire>
	<broadcast>
		<desc>
			You now regret living in a mountain archipelago. For one, most of the pylons to which you wish to connect are thousands of meters away. Worse, though, are that many are across vast stretches of ocean. Yes, you could build cobblestone pillars to raise repeaters from the ocean floor, but you want a solution that is both convenient and does not look ridiculous. To that end, you designed high-power broadcasters, which can send energy over thousands of blocks. However, such power requires a large structure, and that they would interfere if too close to each other.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</broadcast>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
</machines>