<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tools>
	<wand>
		源晶魔杖是你迈向水晶元素与彩能魔法领域的第一步。不论是启动什么仪式，还是更改什么设定，这魔杖似乎都是你操纵方块的主要途径。它似乎还能测试水晶网络的连接，并且能从水晶魔塔中汲取能量到你身上。
	</wand>
	<finder>
		水晶魔塔指南针通过扫描世界中永久存在的魔法能量场并予以分析，籍此来判断距离最近的各元素的水晶魔塔。因为能量一直在波动，所以计算会有些许误差，但只要按照它给出的方向走，即便有误差，再多走几步就能找到。
	</finder>
	<excavator>
		将象征能量与矿物的元素浓缩后，你发现这些东西可以用来挖掘大片区域。你每对地面释放一次能量，这能量似乎只会沿着相同质地的方块传递，但不论如何这都可以让你一次性清理大片岩石、矿石或其它东西。
	</excavator>
	<transition>
		灰色的能量似乎有转变事物的能力，有鉴于此，你开始思考如果将这种能量在这个世界中释放，并给予一些基本信息，比如放置和替换何种方块，这灰色能量应该可以大范围地替换方块，大大加快地面美化速度。
	</transition>
	<invlink>
		Mining and other activities tend to fill your inventory with useless junk that seems to accumulate faster than you can get rid of it. By leveraging the power of elements associated with movement, you discover that you can create a linkage between your inventory and one placed somewhere in the world, and one for which you can control the items it transports.
	</invlink>
	<pendant>
		As you have already discovered, crystallized elemental energy can be found scattered around the world, and its proximity imbues the effects of that element on yourself. However, the effect is rather less than convenient to transport in a form that bulky, so a logical next step would be to wear a small part of the crystal to allow you to benefit from its effects at any location.
	</pendant>
	<vacuumgun>
		Though purely utilitarian ways of killing hostile mobs get the job done, they lack a certain entertainment value. With that in mind, you devised a weapon that creates a rift in the fabric of space, pulling all the creatures into it from a substantial radius. Even better, it seems to rip the blocks out of the ground as well.
	</vacuumgun>
	<lens>
		Crystal Lenses work much like their optical counterparts, focusing, tinting, and otherwise manipulating a beam of energy so that it can apply its effects more strongly over a smaller area.
	</lens>
	<storage>
		Merging small amounts of all the types of crystal yields a crystal that seems to have the ability to store large amounts of energy delivered to it, almost like a battery. This may be convenient for some things that drain this energy yet are too portable for a true crystal network.
	</storage>
	<linktool>
		Many constructs come in pairs, needing to be linked to each other. The linking tool accomplishes exactly that, binding together two positions.
	</linktool>
	<warp>
		By experimenting with the darker aspects of another branch of magic, you have suffered some serious consequences, including impaired vision and a nasty tendency for the air around you to come alive with hostile and destructive manifestations of that power. With this mixture, you should be able to work towards keeping those effects at bay.
	</warp>
	<duplicator>
		Building structures that consist of many repeated parts is a tedious task involving less in the way mental vigour and more in the way of running around. Finally, however, you have found a way to scan regions of a structure and allow it to be replicated as many times as you see fit and can afford.
	</duplicator>
	<teleport>
		Long-distance travel has often been a major headache for you, and even with more advanced powers like gliding and flight, you find yourself spending a great deal of time in transit between distant locations. With the mobility wand, you can fling yourself at a distant location, appearing there instantaneously.
	</teleport>
	<builder>
		Building walls and paths is tedious and time-consuming. Fortunately, with the aid of the construction wand, you can extend any continuous surface you like, greatly expediting this process.
	</builder>
	<capture>
		Moving creatures is nearly impossible. Cows and other animals can be led with food, but they are so stupid that they frequently forget you exist and go wander off a cliff. Wolves have trouble telling the difference between water and lava - which would not be so much of a problem if not for their love of swimming - and cannot find their way through a door if their life depends on it. Finally, most hostile mobs would rather eat/shoot/explode your face than chase you hundreds of blocks. With the capture wand, however, you can ignore these obstacles and carry the mob - in suspension of course - wherever you need.
	</capture>
	<voidcell>
		Your mining efforts have yielded you untold riches in the form of metals, gems, and other materials, but it has also left you with mountains of stone - you literally could build a mountain if you felt like it. Being something of a pack rat, you cannot bring yourself to throw it away, and your crystal-based item storage system is rapidly approaching capacity with some 196 million of it. After some time spent reverse-engineering it, you hit upon a solution. Like the crystal tanks, you could probably use a void link to store basically infinite quantities of an item, though only one item per storage unit.
	</voidcell>
	<aurapouch>
		There are a great many tools available to you to grant you exceptional abilities, including those crystalline pendants you designed earlier. However, each of these needs to remain in your inventory to function. The end result is that your inventory quickly fills while mining, something not helped by the twenty kinds of stone you find underground. Putting these items in a backpack negates their effects, so that is not a solution, either. If only there was some way to put all these items in a bag and still have it pass on the items' effects...
	</aurapouch>
	<multitool>
		不同的方块需要不同的工具来采集，这样才能达到最高效率。若是面对大量五花八门的方块，你肯定也会用上五花八门的工具——镐、斧、锹、剪刀，甚至是剑——接着不断地切换工具就足以让你晕头转向了。似乎，将这些工具融为一体，才是最终的解决方案。
	</multitool>
	<orepick>
		Branch mining is a waste of time. You make a narrow tunnel out of kilometers of rock and find barely anything - and most of what you find is worthless - except that which you blindly dug right into. No doubt large amounts of ore remain hidden to you just underneath the walls of your tunnel, but short of expending the herculean effort to clear all of the overlying stone, you will never know what you are missing...
	</orepick>
	<oresilk>
		You have mechanisms to process ore and increase your rate of return, from half a dozen ways of doubling it to ways of increasing that output even further, but this is rather unhelpful if the ore blocks themselves are unobtainable to you and the ore taunts you by dropping its contents instead. You could of course put Silk Touch on your tool, but enchanting is a random and often frustrating endeavor; a better idea would be to make the tool itself carve ore cleanly from the ground.
	</oresilk>
	<bulkmover>
		You often find yourself scrambling to load many items into a chest that feeds into a machine. The amount of work involved is tedious and frustrating, and a way to expedite the process would be most convenient. The item mover can do just that; it can move large quantities - up to ten thousand - of any one item at a time from one inventory (or digital storage system) to another.
	</bulkmover>
	<chaingun>
		剑与矢对于定点打击很有效，但若是你的目标们分散开来，传统的武器似乎就不太好使了。幸运的是，你的Chain gun发射的子弹可以在目标间来回弹射，甚至能跨越很长一段距离。
	</chaingun>
	<splash>
		For groups of tightly packed mobs, the usual strategy is to wildly flail a sword around you, but this is both rather amateur and ineffective. A weapon that dealt splash damage would be ideal...对于
	</splash>
	<endercrys>
		You recall needing eight of those mysterious pulsing crystals from the eldritch island, but attempting to interact with them blew up in your face...literally. You need a more delicate method of picking them up and storing them.
	</endercrys>
	<hover>
		Water buckets, as a method of breaking fall damage, are somewhat effective, but they require agile reflexes. As a way of climbing a wall, they are slow. Perhaps some sort of magical buffer would do a better job...
	</hover>
	<growth>
		作物生长总是那么缓慢。的确，小麦和那种有着乌黑油亮的种子的作物生长比较快，但是诸如甘蔗之类的就特别慢，Crops take forever to grow. Sure, wheat and that plant with the oily black seeds seem to grow fast enough, but things like sugar cane take hours, and those crops you got to (somehow) drop mob drops and bits of ore take so long you wonder if farming them is even worth the time. You had a watering can which seemed to help, but it got crumpled beyond recognition the moment you tried it with that automated clicking machine. You know that Kijani energy forms the basis of natural things, including plants; perhaps a blast of that may expedite the process.
	</growth>
	<doorkey>
		门总是需要配钥匙的。有鉴于此，你的ethereal barrier需要一把钥匙。按住Shift时手持钥匙右击门，即可将钥匙与门绑定，从而允许你用这把钥匙开门。当然了，这把钥匙不能打开别人的门。
	</doorkey>
	<crystalcell>
		A great many types of items come in sixteen variants, one for each color of crystal energy. Sure, you could just dump them all into your magical etched-crystal storage device, but after mining out a dungeon and finding 23 different tools of six materials (who leaves a bronze sword in a random area underground?), the limit on item types is becoming insurmountable. Perhaps a storage cell dedicated to these crystalline items would mitigate the issue.
	</crystalcell>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
	<name>
		
	</name>
</tools>